{
    "subject": "resource/Bronis\u0142aw_Kaper",
    "predicate": "property/origin",
    "object": "resource/Poland",
    "human_readable": "Bronis\u0142aw Kaper originated from Poland.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9806177020072937,
            "question": "Is Poland associated with Bronis\u0142aw Kaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9762075543403625,
            "question": "Was Bronis\u0142aw Kaper born in Poland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9719455242156982,
            "question": "Where did Bronis\u0142aw Kaper come from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9719226360321045,
            "question": "In what country was Bronis\u0142aw Kaper originally from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.940488874912262,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Bronis\u0142aw Kaper's origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8885223865509033,
            "question": "Is Poland the birthplace of Bronis\u0142aw Kaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8656359314918518,
            "question": "What is the origin of Bronis\u0142aw Kaper's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8409538269042969,
            "question": "What nationality is Bronis\u0142aw Kaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8212109208106995,
            "question": "What is Bronis\u0142aw Kaper known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5845698118209839,
            "question": "Where did Bronis\u0142aw Kaper's musical journey begin?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bronis\u0142aw Kaper originated from Poland.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4500_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Bronis\u0142aw Kaper known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4500_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Bronis\u0142aw Kaper?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4500_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the origin of Bronis\u0142aw Kaper's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4500_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4500_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4500_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4500_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4500_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4500_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4500_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4500_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4500_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4500_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4500_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nAll documents confirm that Bronis\u0142aw Kaper was born in Warsaw, Poland."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided across multiple documents, which indicate that Bronis\u0142aw Kaper was born in Warsaw, Poland and had a significant part of his career there before moving to Berlin and then Hollywood."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}